americanfreight.us 2014-06-18

# Privacy Statement | American Freight

|  | 

[Home](http://www.americanfreight.us/) > Privacy-Statement  
  
---  
  
Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many features.

Information Collected

American Freight® collects personally identifying information as a means to help improve the products and services it offers as well as the content offered on its web sites. The information we collect includes the following:

Personal Information.

American Freight® does not collect any personally identifiable information about you except for the information that you provide to us in order to establish your account, including name, billing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date. We receive, store and use this information to help us communicate with you, respond to your requests and improve the content and services that American Freight® has available.

Other Information.

We collect certain types of other information whenever you access our web sites. This includes the use of “cookies”, which are explained further below, and the information is used to help us provide content specific to your interests.

Electronic Mail Communications.

To enable us to more effectively communicate with our customers, you may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail correspondence, including your account registration, from us. We also may compare our list of e-mail addresses with those of our affiliates in order to avoid duplicative or otherwise unnecessary messages being sent to you.

Information from Other Sources.

To enable us to serve our customers’ needs, we may receive some limited information about you from our affiliates, partners and other third parties. We use the data to ensure the accuracy of our records and we integrate this data with your personal account information.

Use of Information

We intend to use the data provided to us above to operate the web site and to assist us with the delivery of content and other products and services. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary and may be shared with other companies that may want to contact you with offers consistent with your preferences and approval.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

Email addresses obtained may be  used to send promotional emails. Should you no longer want to receive emails from American Freight you can unsubscribe by visiting [this page.](http://www.americanfreight.us/unsubscribe/)

By accessing and using our web sites, you agree that, with respect to other users’ personally identifiable information that you obtain through the Site or through a www.americanfreight.us-related communication or American Freight-facilitated transaction, American Freight® hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for: (a) [www.americanfreight.us-related](http://www.americanfreight.us-related/) communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, and (b) any other purpose that such user expressly opts into after adequate disclosure of the purpose(s). In all cases, you must give users an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this se ction, can you disclose personally identifiable information about another user to any third party without our consent and the consent of such other user after adequate disclosure.

Use of IP Addresses

An IP address is a number assigned to your computer automatically when you access the Internet. Where possible, we may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our site and/or to improve our services to you.

Use of Cookies

We may use cookies on certain pages of our site. We may also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. Among other reasons why we use cookies, cookies allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information which is targeted to your interests or service needs. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning t hat they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session.

Sharing of Information

Your account information is very important to us and we share such information only in limited situations. For example, we may share the information with affiliates of American Freight®, including those entities that control the content on some of our web pages.

Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the gover nment or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company to American Freight® participants as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that you r personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private.

As a general proposition, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.

Security

American Freight® uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, such as firewalls, system security measures and Secure Socket Layers (SSL). Please be advised that “perfect security” does not exist in commercial Internet applications and that such security measures may not prevent all loss, misuse or alteration of information on our web sites.

The registration pages, where you enter your personal and credit card information, are secure. This means that any information you send us is protected by encryption. It is easy to tell when you are protected by encryption – your browser displays a lock or a key which is no longer broken or it changes color when you are on a secure page. The actual icon and its location may vary depending on your browser. For example: Internet Explorer displays a closed padlock at the bottom of the page when a page is secure.

Except as specifically permitted by this section, you may not disclose your American Freight ® password to any third parties nor share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. You may, however, disclose your password to certain third parties with whom American Freight® has entered into specific contractual and technical arrangements designed to safeguard your password (“Authorized Password Users”), in order to enjoy the benefits of those third parti es’ services in relation to the American Freight® services.

Other Web Sites; Links

Our web sites contain links to other third-party Web sites. American Freight® is not responsible for the privacy practices, content, use of cookies or the gathering of other information of such third-party web sites.

Public Forums

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Views reflected in these forums do not reflect the views or opinions of American Freight®. American Freight® reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to move any comments or posts made on its website, for any reason. 

Children

American Freight® does not knowingly collect personal information on children. The content of our web sites and the products and services available are not intended for childre n. If you are under 18, you may only use American Freight® with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice, the practices of this site or your interaction with this web site, please contact info at [contactus@americanfreight.us](mailto:contactus@americanfreight.us)

Third party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively you can point users to opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

**SMS Terms & Conditions**

To stop receiving messages from our SMS shortcode service, reply STOP to any message. To receive more information regarding the SMS shortcode service, reply HELP to any message. The SMS Gateway provider is MessageMedia and provides American Freight with the ability to send SMS messages to the subscribed number for the purpose of delivering opted-in subscribers layaway information regarding payments.

**Message & Data Rates May Apply.**   
If you have questions regarding the service, you may contact American Freight at 740-363-2222 or MessageMedia at +1.866.751.8337. Under normal circumstances we expect to send out no more than 4msgs/month. The American Freight program is designed to notify the subscriber of delinquent layaway payments. It is not binding, and is subject to change without notice. This service may not be available on all carriers. To determine if your carrier is supported, please contact MessageMedia support at +1.866.751.8337.   

Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many features.

Information Collected

American Freight® collects personally identifying information as a means to help improve the products and services it offers as well as the content offered on its web sites. The information we collect includes the following:

Personal Information.

American Freight® does not collect any personally identifiable information about you except for the information that you provide to us in order to establish your account, including name, billing address, credit card number and credit card expiration date. We receive, store and use this information to help us communicate with you, respond to your requests and improve the content and services that American Freight® has available.

Other Information.

We collect certain types of other information whenever you access our web sites. This includes the use of “cookies”, which are explained further below, and the information is used to help us provide content specific to your interests.

Electronic Mail Communications.

To enable us to more effectively communicate with our customers, you may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail correspondence, including your account registration, from us. We also may compare our list of e-mail addresses with those of our affiliates in order to avoid duplicative or otherwise unnecessary messages being sent to you.

Information from Other Sources.

To enable us to serve our customers’ needs, we may receive some limited information about you from our affiliates, partners and other third parties. We use the data to ensure the accuracy of our records and we integrate this data with your personal account information.

Use of Information

We intend to use the data provided to us above to operate the web site and to assist us with the delivery of content and other products and services. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary and may be shared with other companies that may want to contact you with offers consistent with your preferences and approval.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

Email addresses obtained may be  used to send promotional emails. Should you no longer want to receive emails from American Freight you can unsubscribe by visiting [this page.](http://www.americanfreight.us/unsubscribe/)

By accessing and using our web sites, you agree that, with respect to other users’ personally identifiable information that you obtain through the Site or through a www.americanfreight.us-related communication or American Freight-facilitated transaction, American Freight® hereby grants to you a license to use such information only for: (a) [www.americanfreight.us-related](http://www.americanfreight.us-related/) communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, and (b) any other purpose that such user expressly opts into after adequate disclosure of the purpose(s). In all cases, you must give users an opportunity to remove themselves from your database and a chance to review what information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, except as defined in this se ction, can you disclose personally identifiable information about another user to any third party without our consent and the consent of such other user after adequate disclosure.

Use of IP Addresses

An IP address is a number assigned to your computer automatically when you access the Internet. Where possible, we may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our site and/or to improve our services to you.

Use of Cookies

We may use cookies on certain pages of our site. We may also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. Among other reasons why we use cookies, cookies allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information which is targeted to your interests or service needs. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning t hat they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our site and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session.

Sharing of Information

Your account information is very important to us and we share such information only in limited situations. For example, we may share the information with affiliates of American Freight®, including those entities that control the content on some of our web pages.

Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the gover nment or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

Further, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email, and company to American Freight® participants as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that you r personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private.

As a general proposition, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.

Security

American Freight® uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, such as firewalls, system security measures and Secure Socket Layers (SSL). Please be advised that “perfect security” does not exist in commercial Internet applications and that such security measures may not prevent all loss, misuse or alteration of information on our web sites.

The registration pages, where you enter your personal and credit card information, are secure. This means that any information you send us is protected by encryption. It is easy to tell when you are protected by encryption – your browser displays a lock or a key which is no longer broken or it changes color when you are on a secure page. The actual icon and its location may vary depending on your browser. For example: Internet Explorer displays a closed padlock at the bottom of the page when a page is secure.

Except as specifically permitted by this section, you may not disclose your American Freight ® password to any third parties nor share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. You may, however, disclose your password to certain third parties with whom American Freight® has entered into specific contractual and technical arrangements designed to safeguard your password (“Authorized Password Users”), in order to enjoy the benefits of those third parti es’ services in relation to the American Freight® services.

Other Web Sites; Links

Our web sites contain links to other third-party Web sites. American Freight® is not responsible for the privacy practices, content, use of cookies or the gathering of other information of such third-party web sites.

Public Forums

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Views reflected in these forums do not reflect the views or opinions of American Freight®. American Freight® reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to move any comments or posts made on its website, for any reason. 

Children

American Freight® does not knowingly collect personal information on children. The content of our web sites and the products and services available are not intended for childre n. If you are under 18, you may only use American Freight® with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

Questions

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice, the practices of this site or your interaction with this web site, please contact info at [contactus@americanfreight.us](mailto:contactus@americanfreight.us)

Third party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively you can point users to opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

**SMS Terms & Conditions**

To stop receiving messages from our SMS shortcode service, reply STOP to any message. To receive more information regarding the SMS shortcode service, reply HELP to any message. The SMS Gateway provider is MessageMedia and provides American Freight with the ability to send SMS messages to the subscribed number for the purpose of delivering opted-in subscribers layaway information regarding payments.

**Message & Data Rates May Apply.**   
If you have questions regarding the service, you may contact American Freight at 740-363-2222 or MessageMedia at +1.866.751.8337. Under normal circumstances we expect to send out no more than 4msgs/month. The American Freight program is designed to notify the subscriber of delinquent layaway payments. It is not binding, and is subject to change without notice. This service may not be available on all carriers. To determine if your carrier is supported, please contact MessageMedia support at +1.866.751.8337.
